{"data":[{"question":"Mr. Brown is intelligent, and ___ he's very handsome.","a":"what is more","b":"what is worse","c":"as is often the case","d":"which is better","answer":"1","explain":"\n- What is more: used to add more information that emphasizes what you are saying","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"There is no one ___ wishes peace.","a":"who","b":"but","c":"that","d":"whom","answer":"2","explain":"\n - But = Except","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"There is not one of us ___ hopes to help you.","a":"which","b":"whose","c":"whoever","d":"but","answer":"4","explain":"\n- But: used to say that someone has to do something or cannot stop themselves from doing it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"How destructive we are nowadays! \"The next war will be more cruel ___ can be imagined.\"","a":"that","b":"as","c":"than","d":"which","answer":"3","explain":"\n - Than: used when comparing two things, people, situations etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"There is ___ at the news.","a":"no man but who would be surprised","b":"no man but would be surprised","c":"not no man who would be surprised","d":"not any man would be surprised","answer":"2","explain":"\n- But: used to say that someone has to do something or cannot stop themselves from doing it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She is one of the few girls who ___ passed the examination.","a":"was","b":"were","c":"has","d":"have","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense \n- Who= few gilrs= have","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"All history confirms the doctrine that ___ rely upon the sword shall perish by it.","a":"those who","b":"if we","c":"however we","d":"during we","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Those who= those rely upon the sword shall perish by it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The subject ___ I am most interested is English.","a":"in that","b":"in what","c":"in which","d":"in where","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Where (=in\/at which): refers to a place \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person. \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+ We prefer which when the number of choices is limited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"One ___ desires and impulses are not his own has no character.","a":"who","b":"whose","c":"whom","d":"of whom","answer":"2","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She has been suffering from a kind of disease ___.","a":"the cure for which is now possible","b":"whose cure is a recent recovery","c":"whose cure is unable","d":"the cure which is now be done","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}